字幕翻译/压制：旋火
视频来源：youtu.be/DJ70N5HahDU
原视频发布日期：20200501
原作者名：SpaceX
[Music]
[音乐]
Falcon 9 is in startup.
猎鹰9号启动
Dragon is in countdown.
龙飞船开始倒计时
FTS(flight termination system) is armed.
FTS(飞行终止系统)准备完毕
Go for launch.
准备发射
3 2 1 0
Ignition.
点火
Liftoff.
起飞
Super fine and high.
一切良好
Go Falcon. Go Dragon.
去吧 猎鹰和龙
Vehicle is pitching downrange.
猎鹰9号程序转弯
Stage 1 propulsion is nominal.
一级火箭推力正常
Falcon power and telemetry is nominal.
猎鹰9号动力 遥测信号正常
MECO.
一级火箭发动机关闭
Dragon Launch Escape initiated.
龙飞船逃逸系统启动
Draco firing. Everything good.
(超级)天龙座发动机工作中 一切正常
Stage 1 throttle down.
一级火箭节流(?)
[Music]
[音乐]
I see 10m/s horizontally.
水平速度10m/s
[Music]
[音乐]
Good. Main chutes released.
好的 主降落伞释放
Velocity is decreasing.
速度正在减少